

ZAMIR SHAMS

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT INFO

- 00393279984850
- zamir.shams2014@gmail.com
- www.Spartan-Programmer.com
- f www.facebook.com/shamsAN
- @Shams-AN
- 9 83050 AV Italy

SKILLS

JAVASCRIPT
CSS
HTML
SASS
RWD
WEB
LASS

REFERENCES

ЕММА

BOOTSTRAP

Head Coordinator

- **U** 00393386526343
- Emma111@gmail.com

BAHIR ELIAS

QA specialist

- **** 0093730199991
- Bahir014@gmail.com

EDRIS MALYA

Senior Developer

- **** 0093781357171
- Edris.malya@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

I am a confident, motivated graduate that studied computer science faculty and have gotten my specialist in programming after graduation i have started coding with front end of the web so i took the front-end web development as my future career throughout my studies my course has given me experience in coding and programming of the front-end using the basic and fundamentals of the

i specialize mainly in Web dev, i have done some medium projects like CV, portfolio, landing page, static web page etc.I have strong interest in backend languages as well like node.JS, python and java probably ill dive into as will once I am done with frontend.

EXPERIENCE

RANA UNI

2018 - 2019

RANA UNIVERSITY

2019 - 2020

MENDU

2020 - 2021

INTERN

As I joined in Rana university as intern it was really helpful for me as intern I learned so many things form that time working with peers together and using others.

JUNIOR WEB DEV

Being as junior it much significant to learn new things along with others step by step it was really wondering I was working with new technologies of web.

FRONT-END WEB DEV

Working as front-end web developer needs much hard work, I was responsible for the all front-ends and all management for the national defense university.

EDUCATION

GHULAM HAIDAR KHAN HIGH SCHOOL

1999 - 2011

TECH COLLAGE INDIA

2014 - 2016

RANA UNIVERSITY

2018 - 2021

SCHOOL

In school period we used to study the basic subject related to school and running on top of the rankin it just gave the knowledge of the overall technologies.

MANAGEMENT.CYBER SEC

Cyber security is one of the most top major in the world I just learned the basics of the cyber security in India, it really helps to expand the tech enhancement.

COMPUTER SCIENCE (B.S.E)

Actually in university we just view all the basics of the programming and development so that each student can take their own interest to respective field.

AWARDS

BEST TEACHER MEDAL

jan 2017

EXCELLENT WORK

Due to evaluation of the Academy the seniors used to give the merit certificate to one who deserve it, fortunately I succeeded to gain on of the medals

TOP RUNNER MEDAL

jan 2017

OUTSTANDING PERFORMANCE

As a result of best work among the team its really pleasure to gain the top score of the team due to high and best performance in any field of the organization.